[1] B. Yang, J. Yan, Z. Lei, and S. Z. Li, “Aggregate channel eatures for multi-view face detection,” in IEEE International Joint Conference on Biometrics, 2014, pp. 1-8.

[2] P. Viola and M. J. Jones, “Robust real-time face detection. International journal of computer vision,” vol. 57, no. 2, pp. 137-154, 2004 

[3] M. T. Pham, Y. Gao, V. D. D. Hoang, and T. J. Cham, “Fast polygonal integration and its application in extending haar-like features to improve object detection,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2010, pp. 942-949. 

[4] Q. Zhu, M. C. Yeh, K. T. Cheng, and S. Avidan, “Fast human detection using a cascade of histograms of oriented gradients,” in IEEE Computer Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2006, pp. 1491-1498. 

[5] M. Mathias, R. Benenson, M. Pedersoli, and L. Van Gool, “Face detection without bells and whistles,” in European Conference on Computer Vision, 2014, pp. 720-735. 

[6] J. Yan, Z. Lei, L. Wen, and S. Li, “The fastest deformable part model for object detection,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2014, pp. 2497-2504. 

[7] X. Zhu, and D. Ramanan, “Face detection, pose estimation, and landmark localization in the wild,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2012, pp. 2879-2886. 

[8] M. Köstinger, P. Wohlhart, P. M. Roth, and H. Bischof, “Annotated facial landmarks in the wild: A large-scale, real-world database for facial landmark localization,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition Workshops, 2011, pp. 2144-2151. 

[9] A. Krizhevsky, I. Sutskever, and G. E. Hinton, “Imagenet classification with deep convolutional neural networks,” in Advances in neural information processing systems, 2012, pp. 1097-1105. 

[10] Y. Sun, Y. Chen, X. Wang, and X. Tang, “Deep learning face representation by joint identification-verification,” in Advances in Neural Information Processing Systems, 2014, pp. 1988-1996. 

[11] S. Yang, P. Luo, C. C. Loy, and X. Tang, “From facial parts responses to face detection: A deep learning approach,” in IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision, 2015, pp. 3676-3684. 

[12] X. P. Burgos-Artizzu, P. Perona, and P. Dollar, “Robust face landmark estimation under occlusion,” in IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision, 2013, pp. 1513-1520. 

[13] X. Cao, Y. Wei, F. Wen, and J. Sun, “Face alignment by explicit shape regression,” International Journal of Computer Vision, vol 107, no. 2, pp. 177-190, 2012. 

[14] T. F. Cootes, G. J. Edwards, and C. J. Taylor, “Active appearance models,” IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence, vol. 23, no. 6, pp. 681-685, 2001. 

[15] X. Yu, J. Huang, S. Zhang, W. Yan, and D. Metaxas, “Pose-free facial landmark fitting via optimized part mixtures and cascaded deformable shape model,” in IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision, 2013, pp. 1944-1951. 

[16] J. Zhang, S. Shan, M. Kan, and X. Chen, “Coarse-to-fine auto-encoder networks (CFAN) for real-time face alignment,” in European Conference on Computer Vision, 2014, pp. 1-16. 

[17] Luxand Incorporated: Luxand face SDK, http://www.luxand.com/ 

[18] D. Chen, S. Ren, Y. Wei, X. Cao, and J. Sun, “Joint cascade face detection and alignment,” in European Conference on Computer Vision, 2014, pp. 109-122. 

[19] H. Li, Z. Lin, X. Shen, J. Brandt, and G. Hua, “A convolutional neural network cascade for face detection,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2015, pp. 5325-5334. 

[20] C. Zhang, and Z. Zhang, “Improving multiview face detection with multi-task deep convolutional neural networks,” IEEE Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision, 2014, pp. 1036-1041. 

[21] X. Xiong, and F. Torre, “Supervised descent method and its applications to face alignment,” in IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition, 2013, pp. 532-539. 

[22] Z. Zhang, P. Luo, C. C. Loy, and X. Tang, “Facial landmark detection by deep multi-task learning,” in European Conference on Computer Vision, 2014, pp. 94-108. 

[23] Z. Liu, P. Luo, X. Wang, and X. Tang, “Deep learning face attributes in the wild,” in IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision, 2015, pp. 3730-3738. 

[24] S. Yang, P. Luo, C. C. Loy, and X. Tang, “WIDER FACE: A Face Detection Benchmark”. arXiv preprint arXiv:1511.06523. 

[25] V. Jain, and E. G. Learned-Miller, “FDDB: A benchmark for face detection in unconstrained settings,” Technical Report UMCS-2010-009, University of Massachusetts, Amherst, 2010. 

[26] B. Yang, J. Yan, Z. Lei, and S. Z. Li, “Convolutional channel features,” in IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision, 2015, pp. 82-90. 

[27] R. Ranjan, V. M. Patel, and R. Chellappa, “A deep pyramid deformable part model for face detection,” in IEEE International Conference on Biometrics Theory, Applications and Systems, 2015, pp. 1-8. 

[28] G. Ghiasi, and C. C. Fowlkes, “Occlusion Coherence: Detecting and Localizing Occluded Faces,” arXiv preprint arXiv:1506.08347. 

[29] S. S. Farfade, M. J. Saberian, and L. J. Li, “Multi-view face detection using deep convolutional neural networks,” in ACM on International Conference on Multimedia Retrieval, 2015, pp. 643-650. 
