1611.05271@：DeMeshNet: Blind Face Inpainting for Deep MeshFace Veriﬁcation
==>1606.08921：Image Restoration Using Convolutional Auto-encoders with Symmetric Skip Connections
==>1604.07379：Context Encoders: Feature Learning by Inpainting
==>1412.6572：EXPLAINING AND HARNESSING ADVERSARIAL EXAMPLES
      1412.1897：Deep Neural Networks are Easily Fooled: High Conﬁdence Predictions for Unrecognizable Images
      1312.6199：Intriguing properties of neural networks
==>1506.02025@：Spatial Transformer Networks
==>1606.00373#：Deeper Depth Prediction with Fully Convolutional Residual Networks
      ==>1411.5928@：Learning to Generate Chairs, Tables and Cars with Convolutional Networks
==>1411.4038@：Fully Convolutional Networks for Semantic Segmentation
      1605.06211@：Fully Convolutional Networks for Semantic Segmentation
==>1505.07293@：SegNet: A Deep Convolutional Encoder-Decoder Architecture for Robust Semantic Pixel-Wise Labelling
      1511.00561@：SegNet: A Deep Convolutional Encoder-Decoder Architecture for Image Segmentation
==>1505.04366@：Learning Deconvolution Network for Semantic Segmentation
==>1603.08155@：Perceptual Losses for Real-Time Style Transfer and Super-Resolution
==>1409.5185@：Deeply-Supervised Nets
