1701.07274：DEEP REINFORCEMENT LEARNING: AN OVERVIEW
1604.07379/cvpr16：Context Encoders: Feature Learning by Inpainting
1607.07539：Semantic Image Inpainting with Deep Generative Models
1609.04802：Photo-Realistic Single Image Super-Resolution Using a GAN
1611.09969：High-Resolution Image Inpainting using Multi-Scale Neural Patch Synthesis
1612.00005：Plug & Play Generative Networks: Conditional Iterative Generation of Images in Latent Space
1701.00160：NIPS 2016 Tutorial: Generative Adversarial Networks
1703.06211：Deformable Convolutional Networks
1703.06870：Mask R-CNN
1711.10925/Deep_Image_Prior：Deep Image Prior
1804.07723：Image Inpainting for Irregular Holes Using Partial Convolutions
1712.04646：Learning Disentangling and Fusing Networks for Face Completion Under Structured Occlusions
1611.05271：DeMeshNet: Blind Face Inpainting for Deep MeshFace Veriﬁcation
===================
1608.00207：LEARNING DEEP REPRESENTATION FROM COARSE TO FINE FOR FACE ALIGNMENT
1604.02878：Joint Face Detection and Alignment using Multi-task Cascaded Convolutional Networks
1408.3967：Learning Deep Representation for Face Alignment with Auxiliary Attributes
1406.4773：Deep Learning Face Representation by Joint Identiﬁcation-Veriﬁcation
